// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The following are types of speech according to purpose EXCEPT __________.",
    answer: "b. impromptu speech",
    options: [
      "a. informative speech",
      "b. impromptu speech",
      "c. persuasive speech",
      "d. entertainment speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Below are the types of speech according to delivery EXCEPT __________.",
    answer: "c. persuasive speech",
    options: [
      "a. impromptu speech",
      "b. extemporaneous speech",
      "c. persuasive speech",
      "d. manuscript speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The primary goal of a/an ___________ is to influence the thoughts, feelings, actions, and behaviors or attitudes of your listeners (Gamble & Gamble, 2012).",
    answer: "c. persuasive speech",
    options: [
      "a. informative speech",
      "b. expository speech",
      "c. persuasive speech",
      "d. entertainment speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The type of speech that aims to make the audience relax, enjoy, and even laugh is called ___________.",
    answer: "d. informative speech",
    options: [
      "a. expository speech",
      "b. persuasive speech",
      "c. entertainment speech",
      "d. informative speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Delivering a speech with the help of short notes and a clear outline is known as _________.",
    answer: "b. extemporaneous speech",
    options: [
      "a. manuscript speech",
      "b. extemporaneous speech",
      "c. memorized speech",
      "d. impromptu speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "When you deliver a pre-written speech word for word, it is called __________.",
    answer: "a. impromptu speech",
    options: [
      "a. impromptu speech",
      "b. memorized speech",
      "c. manuscript speech",
      "d. extemporaneous speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A/ an __________ is delivered with little or no advance preparation.",
    answer: "a. impromptu speech",
    options: [
      "a. impromptu speech",
      "b. memorized speech",
      "c. manuscript speech",
      "d. extemporaneous speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The nature of a reporter’s job is to give an expository or __________.",
    answer: "a. persuasive speech",
    options: [
      "a. persuasive speech",
      "b. informative speech",
      "c. manuscript speech",
      "d. impromptu speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The President follows a/an __________ during his State of the Nation Address (SONA) so as not to miss any important detail.",
    answer: "c. memorized speech",
    options: [
      "a. entertainment speech",
      "b. impromptu speech",
      "c. memorized speech",
      "d. manuscript speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The Department of Health (DOH) Spokesperson transitioned from manuscript speech to __________ when she answered various pressing questions during the media press conference.",
    answer: "a. extemporaneous speech",
    options: [
      "a. extemporaneous speech",
      "b. memorized speech",
      "c. impromptu speech",
      "d. entertainment speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Jeff tried out an online interview which tested his skill in__________.",
    answer: "a. impromptu speech",
    options: [
      "a. impromptu speech",
      "b. informative speech",
      "c. memorized speech",
      "d. entertainment speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The type of speech that appeals to the audience’s emotion and provides striking statistics to support the ideas is called __________.",
    answer: "b. persuasive speech",
    options: [
      "a. informative speech",
      "b. persuasive speech",
      "c. manuscript speech",
      "d. extemporaneous speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Knowing your audience well will be most useful in a/an __________.",
    answer: "a. informative speech",
    options: [
      "a. informative speech",
      "b. entertainment speech",
      "c. memorized speech",
      "d. manuscript speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The speaker’s credibility is highly important in a/an __________.",
    answer: "b. memorized speech",
    options: [
      "a. manuscript speech",
      "b. memorized speech",
      "c. entertainment speech",
      "d. persuasive speech"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Incorporating gestures, facial expressions, and movements in your _________ can help avoid unnatural delivery.",
    answer: "d. extemporaneous speech",
    options: [
      "a. manuscript speech",
      "b. impromptu speech",
      "c. memorized speech",
      "d. extemporaneous speech"
    ]
  },
];
